My name's Conan Edogawa.
اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a pill that shrunk him!
أُجبر الطالب في الثانوية كودو شينتشي على تجرّع عقار قلّص جسده
I may look like a little grade school student,
قد أبدو بمظهر صغير في الابتدائية
but my powers of deduction are unrivaled!
لكنّ تحليلي لا مثيل له
I'll show you how mysteries are really solved!
!سأريكم كيف تُحلّ الألغاز
Today's incident is a terrifying explosion on a bullet train!
حادثة اليوم هي انفجار مريع !على متن قطار طلقة
Nobody shaves in the bullet train
...لا أحد يحلق على متن قطار الطلقة في طريقه
on the way to their best friend's wedding!
لزفاف صديقه المقرب
It's not my fault!
!لم يكن بيدي حيلة
I overslept 'cuz I was up late last night discussing things with a client!
أطلت في النوم لأني سهرت !ليلاً أتناقش مع عميل
Oh, please. You got drunk and fell asleep in the doorway.
تقول ذلك، لكنك ثملت ونمت في الممر
I brought you along 'cuz you wanted to come, but I dunno why...
...جلبتك معي لأنك أردتِ القدوم، لكن لا أدري لمَ
But the wedding's in Kyoto!
!الزفاف في طوكيو
You really wanted to go there too, didn't you, Conan-kun?
أردتَ الذهاب هناك أيضاً، صحيح يا كونان-كن؟
Yeah.
أجل
Why did we have to bring him along anyway?!
لمَ جلبناه بالأصل؟
You know we can't leave him all alone!
!لا يمكننا تركه بمفرده
Say, are those new shoes?
لحظة، أليس هذا حذاءً جديداً؟
Yeah! Professor Agasa gave them to me!
بلى، أعطاني إيّاه البروفسور آغاسا
I made you something I'm sure you'll like!
اخترعتُ شيئاً سيعجبك
Power Kick Shoes!
!حذاء مضاعفة قوّة الركل
Kick a ball with these shoes
إن ركلت كرةً بهذا الحذاء
and the criminals won't know what hit them!
!لن يعرف المجرمون ما أصابهم
It uses electricity and magnetic fields to stimulate your feet muscles,
يستعمل الكهرباء والمجال المغناطيسي لتحفيز عضلات قدمك
thereby substantially increasing your kick power!
!فيضاعف قوّة ركلك لحدٍّ كبير
What about my glasses?
ماذا عن النظارات؟
They're ready too.
جاهزة أيضاً
I added a miniature hidden microphone to them.
أضفتُ ميكروفوناً صغيراً مخفياً بها
I'm certain it'll come in handy!
سيكون ذا فائدة حتماً
I hope they actually work when I need them to!
آمل أن يعمل متى احتجت له
A bullet train!
!قطار طلقة
But why are they with us too?!
!لكن لمَ أتوا هم أيضاً؟
What does it matter? Their tickets have been paid for.
ما المشكلة؟ دُفعت تذاكرهم
Man, parents these days...
يا إلهي، ما خطب آباء هذه الأيام؟
Conan-kun! Let's go exploring!
!لنذهب للاستكشاف يا كونان-كن
It looks like it'll be really fun!
!يبدو أنّه سيكون مسلياً كثيراً
Let's go!
!هيّا بنا
Their parents obviously have some issues.
لدى آبائهم مشاكل حقاً
And what about his parents?!
لكن ماذا عن والديه؟
They haven't even called us once!
لم يتّصلوا بنا ولو لمرّة حتى
Uh oh!
!تباً
I gotta go to the bathroom!
!سأذهب للحمام قليلاً
It's not like I'm living with you because I want to!
!لا أسكن معكم لأنّي أريد ذلك
It's all their fault!
!إنها غلطتهما
They were the ones who forced me to take that weird pill
كانا من أجبرني على تجرّع ذاك العقار الغريب
and wind up small like this!
!وقلّصا جسدي هكذا
It's them!
!إنّهما هما
This is my best chance to steal some of those pills!
!أفضل فرصة لسرقة ذاك العقار
Once I turn back into high school detective Shinichi Kudo,
،حالما أرجع متحري الثانوية كودو شينتشي
I'll expose all of your evil deeds to the world!
!سأكشف كلّ أفعالكم الشريرة للعالم
Just you wait!
!بلا ريب
But what in the world could they be doing here?
لكن ما الذي يفعلانه هنا؟
They're meeting with someone...
يلتقيان أحدهم
Now's my chance to plant Professor Agasa's hidden microphone
الآن فرصتي لتثبيت ميكروفون البروفسور المخفي
on one of their seats!
!بأحد مقاعدهم
What are you doing, Conan-kun?!
!ما الذي تفعله يا كونان-كن؟
Move!
ابتعد قليلاً
I wasn't doing anything...
...لم أكن أفعل
Really?
حقّاً؟
You're such a troublemaker, Conan-kun!
يا لك من مشاغب يا كونان-كن
It's people like you who give kids a bad name!
أمثالك هم من يسيئون لسمعة الصغار
You should wrap the gum in paper and put it in an ashtray!
!عليك لفّ العلكة بورقة ووضعها في المنفضة
There.
هكذا
I'll hear them just fine if it's in there!
سأسمعهما كما يجب إن كانت هنا
Learn from your friends, Conan-kun!
تعلّم من أصدقائك يا كونان-كن
You're all such good children!
أنتم أطفال مهذبون
Of course we are!
!بالطبع
Let's go!
!هيّا بنا
If I know you, Conan-kun, that wasn't any ordinary prank!
لم يكن مجرد مقلب عادي بما أنّه !من تدبيرك يا كونان-كن
Was that gum some sort of secret weapon?!
أكانت تلك العلكة سلاحاً سرّياً ما؟
Are those two men spies?! Hit men?!
هل ذلكما الاثنان جاسوسان؟ قاتلان مستأجران؟
It would be great if they were, but I was just being a troublemaker!
!كان ذلك ليكون مسلياً، لكني كنتُ أشاغب قليلاً فقط
For reals?
حقّاً؟
Aw, man...
...هكذا إذاً
What a bore. Let's get back to exploring!
!مُمل، لنرجع للاستكشاف
Excuse me for being a bore.
أعتذر على كوني مُملاً
Outta the way, boy.
ابتعد يا صبيّ
Huh?
ماذا؟
It's not them! They're not the men in black!
!ليسا هما، ليسا الرجلين بالرداء الأسود
I got the wrong people! I feel like such an idiot!
!أخطأتُ في التعرف عليهما! يا لحماقتي
He has a suitcase instead of the attaché case he had before...
...يحمل حقيبة سفر بدل حقيبة الورق التي كانت معه
Something's not right...
هناك خطبٌ ما
The two suitcases are too different
الحقيبتان مختلفتان كثيراً فلا يمكن أن تخطئ في أخذ واحدة مكان الأخرى
That's it! I'll use the professor's hidden microphone!
!صحيح! سأستعمل ميكروفون البروفسور المخفي
He said that if I turn the dial to match the frequency,
،قال إن أدرت القرص لمطابقة التردد
special sound waves will stimulate my eardrums,
فستحفّز موجات صوت خاصة طبلات أذني
allowing me to hear with my glasses on!
!ويمكنني السماع أثناء ارتداء نظّارتي
I can finally have a smoke.
يمكنني التدخين أخيراً
I can hear them!
!أسمعهما
Something's in here!
!يوجد شيءٌ هنا
Oh no!
!تبّاً
Oh, it's just gum.
ماذا؟ مجرد علكة
That was close!
كان ذلك وشيكاً
This sure turned out to be an easy transaction, boss!
كانت صفقةً سهلة في النهاية يا أخي
Keep it down!
أخفض صوتك
Don't worry, nobody's listening!
لا تقلق، لا أحد يستمع
But 100 million just for handing over that case?
لكن مئة مليون مقابل تسليم تلك الحقيبة فقط؟
What in the world was inside it?
ما كان بها بالضبط؟
Information about gold.
معلومات عن الذهب
Information that's worth more than 100 million once it's put to use.
معلومات تفوق قيمتها مئة مليون إن اُستعملت
Probably's already sitting back down, smiling with glee
لعلّه جالسٌ الآن والابتسامة تمتد على وجهه
and looking out at the last scenic view that the fool will ever get to see...
...بينما ينظر لآخر منظر طبيعيّ سيراه عبر النافذة
Last scenic view?
آخر منظر؟
Included inside the black case we handed over...
...يوجد داخل الحقيبة السوداء التي أعطيناه إياها
...was a bomb that'll detonate in 10 seconds after receiving a large shock!
قنبلة ستنفجر في 10 ثوانٍ حال تلقي صدمة قوية
A bomb?!
!قـ-قنبلة؟
So if they accidentally drop the case...
...إن حدث وأسقط الحقيبة أيضاً
The information is too important.
تلك المعلومة مهمة جداً له
I doubt that would happen...
أشكّ بحصول ذلك
And besides, the explosion is set for 3:10.
كما أن الانفجار مؤقت على 3:10
It's a time bomb?
قنبلة مؤقتة؟
No. But when the time comes,
كلا، لكن عندما يحين الوقت
they'll unknowingly press the detonation button themselves.
سيضغط مفتاح التفجير دون أن يدرك
10 seconds later, the entire bullet train gets blasted into pieces.
وفي غضون 10 ثوانٍ، سينفجر قطار الطلقة لأجزاء
Into pieces?!
!لـ-لأجزاء؟
I mean, 8 times 8 equals?
أ-أقصد ثمانية ضرب ثمانية؟
64!
!‏64
Don't you mean "Happa 64"?
ألا تقصد "هابّا 64"؟
Oh, right!
!صحيح
8 times 8 is 64!
!ثمانية ضرب ثمانية تساوي 64
8 times 9...
...ثمانية ضرب تسعة
72!
!‏72
Stupid kid had me scared there for a second!
...أخافني ذاك الصبيّ
Now arriving at Nagoya!
!وصلنا ناغويا! ناغويا
Hurry! We're getting off!
!أسرع! سننزل
Wait! There's still something I want to ask you!
!انتظرا! لا يزال هناك ما أريد سؤالكما عنه
Wait!
!انتظرا
Not so fast!
!أنت
I can't let you out of my sight, Conan-kun.
لا يمكنني إشاحة نظري عنك يا كونان-كن
This is bad! Without them onboard--
...هذا سيّئ، دون وجودهما
Wait. The person they made the transaction with is still inside!
لحظة، لا يزال الطرف الآخر في صفقتهما موجوداً هنا
Oh, man! 40 minutes until it explodes!
!تبّاً، 40 دقيقة حتّى الانفجار
I have to find the person before then!
!عليّ إيجاد الشخص قبل ذلك
But how?! There's hundreds of passengers onboard!
!لكن كيف؟ يوجد مئات الركاب، فكيف؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Where could he have gone...
أين ذهب؟
A bomb?!
!قـ-قنبلة؟
Yeah! Someone onboard has a bomb!
!أجل! أحد الركاب معه قنبلة
We have to stop the train at the next station
علينا إيقاف القطار في المحطة التالية
and evacuate all the passengers!
!وإخلاء كافة الركاب
This train's gonna be blown to smithereens!
!سينفجر هذا القطار لأجزاء
Now, now. Don't be teasing grownups.
لا تضايق الكبار يا فتى
Hold on. It isn't nice to disregard him just because he's a kid.
انتظر، ليس لطيفاً تجاهله لأنه طفل فقط
Wait a second while I call Anpan Man for help!
انتظرني يا بنيّ، سأتصل الآن بـ "آنبان مان" لطلب المساعدة
No good! They don't believe me one bit!
لا جدوى، لا يصدقونني أبداً
What should I do?!
ماذا أفعل؟
Conan-kun! Is anything interesting going on?
كونان-كن! أهناك أمرٌ مثير يجري؟
Let us know if you find another case to solve!
!أخبرنا إن وجدت قضيّة أخرى
Are these the only guys who'll listen to me?!
أهؤلاء كلّ من لديّ بصفي؟
There are tons of black briefcases...
توجد عشرات الحقائب السوداء
Checking them all would be impossible!
وتفقّدها جميعاً مستحيل
Darn it! Is my only option to look for the bomb alone?
تبّاً، هل خياري الوحيد البحث عن القنبلة بمفردي؟
Find a clue!
جد خيطاً
Remember back to the beginning of their conversation!
!تذكّر بداية محادثتهما
I can finally have a smoke.
يمكنني التدخين أخيراً
What does that mean?
ما قصده بذلك؟
The dining car isn't non-smoking...
التدخين ليس محظوراً في عربة الطعام
Ah! The person they met doesn't like cigarette smoke!
!هكذا إذاً! الطرف الآخر يكره دخان السجائر
Meaning that person doesn't smoke!
!أي أنّه لا يدخن
Which means the person's in a non-smoking car!
!مما يعني أنّه في عربة لا تدخين
Let's see, how many non-smoking cars were on this train...?
حسناً، كم عدد عربات اللا تدخين الإجمالي في هذا القطار؟
Eight!
!ثمان
Why do you ask?
لمَ تسأل؟
Are we solving a mystery?!
أتحلّ لغزاً؟
There have to be more clues!
لا بد من وجود خيوط أكثر
100 million just for handing over that case?
مئة مليون مقابل تسليم تلك الحقيبة فقط؟
What in the world was inside it?
ما كان بها بالضبط؟
Information about gold.
معلومات عن الذهب
Probably's already sitting back down, smiling with glee
لعلّه جالسٌ الآن والابتسامة ترتسم على وجهه
and looking out at the last scenic view that the fool will ever get to see...
...بينما ينظر لآخر منظر طبيعيّ سيراه عبر النافذة
Where on this train can you see scenic views from the windows?!
أين يمكنك رؤية مناظر طبيعية من النوافذ في القطار؟
The 2-story Green Cars!
!العربات الخضراء بالطابقين
There are 3 Green Cars, right? Which ones are non-smoking?
توجد 3 عربات خضراء، صحيح؟ أيّها محظورة التدخين؟
That would be the 2nd floor of Car 7!
!كانت... الطابق الثاني من العربة السابعة
What's there?!
!ماذا هناك؟
I dunno what's goin' on, but let's go anyway!
!لا أدري ما الذي يجري لكن لنذهب بأيّ حال
No, it's too dangerous for children...
كلا، ذلك خطير على الأطفال
We're the Junior Detective Club! Let's go!
!نحن فرقة فتيان التحرّي! هيّا بنا
Who could have the black briefcase with the bomb in it?!
من يحمل الحقيبة السوداء التي تحمل القنبلة؟
One...
...واحد
Two...
...اثنان
Three...
...ثلاثة
Four...
...أربعة
I'll have to check them each one by one!
عليّ التحقق منهم جميعاً
Stock trading and a gold Rolex!
!تداول أسهم... وروليكس ذهبية
He's rakin' in the dough, all right...
إنّه يرقد بين النقود حقّاً
Here goes!
حسنٌ
Hey! Can I play that game too?
أخبرني، أيمكنني اللعب معك؟
This is not a toy!
!إنّها ليست لعبة
Liar! There's a bunch of circles and rectangles on the screen!
!كاذب! توجد مجموعة دوائر ومثلثات على الشاشة
You're disrupting my work! Go away!
!أنت تعترض عملي! ارحل
Big meanie!
!لئيم
Then let me play this black one! It's a game too, right?
دعني ألعب بهذا الأسود إذاً، إنه لعبة كذلك، صحيح؟
What's the matter, little boy? Are you lost?
ما الخطب يا فتى؟ أضللت طريقك؟
Wow!
!مُذهل
What a good view this is!
!منظر جميل
Isn't it? The weather is clear today, so you can see Mt. Fuji from there!
أجل، الطقس صحو اليوم لذا يمكنك رؤية جبل فوجي من هنا
Mt. Fuji?!
جبل فوجي؟
Do you like Mt. Fuji?
أتحب جبل فوجي يا فتى؟
Yeah! I love it!
!أجل، أحبه كثيراً
Darn! It's locked!
!تبّاً! إنها مقفلة
Shut up already! What part of "go away" don't you understand?!
!اخرس! ماذا لا تفهم في "ارحل"؟
Ugh.
تبّاً
Say, did you go to the dining car?
أخبريني يا عمّة، أذهبتِ لعربة الطعام؟
Eh? Why do you ask?
لمَ تسأل؟
I just thought you looked like the person who was there
ظننتك تشبهين من كان رفقة
with some men dressed in black.
الاثنين بالرداء الأسود
Oh, you must have the wrong person then.
أخطأت في الشخص إذاً
I haven't been to the dining car.
لم أذهب لعربة الطعام
What about you, Mister?
ماذا عنك يا عم؟
As if I could go anywhere when I'm this busy!
!كأن بإمكاني الذهاب لمكان وأنا مشغول هكذا
Sorry!
!آسف
Hey, did you go to the dining car a little while ago?
أخبرني، هل ذهبت لعربة الطعام قبل قليل؟
Huh?
ماذا؟
I said, did you go to the dining car a little while ago?!
!سألتك إن كنت ذهبت لعربة الطعام قبل قليل؟
Why, yes I did!
!أجل، ذهبت
No matter how many times I go, Disneyland is always fun!
!مهما ذهبت من مرّات، "ديزني لاند" مسلية دوماً
This isn't working out. I'll come back to him later!
لا جدوى... حسناً، سأعود له لاحقاً
Gold rims!
!إطار ذهبي
Hey! Did you go to the dining car?
هل ذهبت لعربة الطعام قبل قليل؟
What?
ماذا؟
That's a napkin from the dining car!
!إنه منديل مائدة من عربة الطعام
This guy's been there!
!كان هذا الشخص هناك
Here goes!
حسنٌ
Hey, my paper airplane got stuck up there.
علقت طائرتي الورقية هناك
You don't mind if I get it, do you?
لا تمانع إن أخذتها، صحيح؟
Okay?
لا مشكلة؟
Huh? Where is it? I can't find it!
ماذا؟ أين هي؟ لا أجدها
Don't touch that!
!لا تلمسها
Included inside the black case we handed over...
...يوجد داخل الحقيبة السوداء التي أعطيناه إيّاها
...was a bomb that'll detonate in 10 seconds after receiving a large shock!
قنبلة ستنفجر في 10 ثوانٍ حال تلقي صدمة قوية
Oh no!
!تبّاً
Nice catch, Genta-kun!
!التقاط ممتاز يا غينتا-كن
Excellent job!
!مذهل
What is this, anyway?
ما هذا بأيّ حال؟
It's a--
...إ-إنّها
Will you knock it off already?!
!هلّا توقفت؟
Underwear?!
سـ-سروال داخلي؟
You lousy kids!
!أيّها الأشقياء
And stay out!
!لا ترجعوا
Conan-kun! The rest of you too! Give it a rest!
!كونان-كن! أنتم أيضاً! يكفي عبثاً
14 minutes until it explodes!
!بقي 11 دقيقة حتى الانفجار
But that's one person down! Only three to go!
لكن تقلص عددهم بواحد على الأقل، تبقى ثلاثة
Who has the bomb?!
!من يحمل القنبلة؟
Darn those freaks!
!تبّاً لهما
It's a time bomb?
قنبلة مؤقتة؟
No. But when the time comes,
،كلا، لكن عندما يحين الوقت
they'll unknowingly press the detonation button themselves.
سيضغط مفتاح التفجير دون أن يدرك
That's it!
!ها هي
That means the explosion's set off by the person's reaction to something...
...ما يعني أن الانفجار سيحدث بردة فعل الشخص لشيء
The 3 people have a laptop, a cell phone, and a tape player!
،بحوزة الثلاثة أشخاص... حاسب محمول هاتف خلوي، ومشغل صوت بسمّاعات
No good! They're all suspect!
!لا جدوى! كلّهم مشتبه به
I'm still missing something!
لا يزال ينقصني خيط
No you don't! Where do you think you're going?
توقف! أين ستذهب؟
I told you to sit here and behave yourself!
أخبرتك أن تبقى مكانك
But I need to go to the bathroom...
...لكن عليّ الذهاب للحمّام
You just went.
ذهبت قبل قليل
I'm thirsty--
أشعر بالعطش
Just put up with it.
تحمّل فقط
Gifts?
هدايا؟
You're supposed to buy those on your way back!
تشتريها في طريق عودتك
A walk?
تجوّل؟
No!
!كلا
You sure do like to get into trouble...
...تحب إثارة الشغب حقّاً
Oh no! 7 minutes left!
!تبّاً! تبقت 7 دقائق
The only choice now is to explain everything
ليس أمامي الآن سوى شرح كلّ شيء
and have all the passengers evacuate!
وجعل الركاب يخلون القطار
But nobody'll believe me because I'm a kid!
!لكن لا أحد يصدقني لأني طفل
There's only one way to make her believe me!
هناك طريقة واحدة فقط لجعلها تصدقني
If I tell her that I'm actually Shinichi Kudo,
،لو أخبرتها أنّ هويتي هي كودو شينتشي
Ran would have to believe me!
!ستصدقني ران
Everyone would believe her if she told them!
!عندها سيصدق الجميع كلامها
If the bomb explodes, me, Ran, and all the other passengers are...
...إن انفجرت القنبلة، سأكون وران وجميع الركاب
Say, Ran.
...ران، أنا
That's no way to address your elders!
!ليس هكذا، نادني ران-نيتشان
You're supposed to use name suffixes for older people!
يُفترض أن تستعمل اللّواحق عند مخاطبة من أهم أكبر سنّاً منك
Listen to me, Ran.
أصغي لي يا ران
You did it again!
!ها أنت مجدداً
This is serious!
!أنا أتكلم بجدية
I'm sorry, Ran.
آسف يا ران
I've been hiding something from you this whole time.
كنت أخفي أمراً عنك
Hiding?
تخفي؟
I'm neither Conan Edogawa nor a grade school student!
...لستُ إيدوغاوا كونان أو طالباً في الابتدائية
I'm...
...أنا
I'm actually...
...أنا في الواقع
Yeah, while you were looking away.
أجل، بينما كنت تنظر بعيداً
But these seats face the mountains!
لكن هذه المقاعد تقابلها الجبال
We wouldn't have seen it anyway!
فلم نكن لنراه بأيّ حال
Facing the mountains?!
مقابل الجبال؟
What a good view this is!
!منظر جميل
Isn't it? The weather is clear today so you can see Mt. Fuji from there!
أجل، الطقس صحو اليوم لذا يمكنك رؤية جبل فوجي من هنا
I'm sure those seats faced the ocean!
...كانت تلك المقاعد مقابل المحيط
It would be impossible to see Mt. Fuji!
لذا من المستحيل أن ترى جبل فوجي
Then where did she see Mt. Fuji from?
من أين رأتْه إذاً؟
The dining car!
!عربة الطعام
They sat on the side facing the mountains.
جلسوا على الجانب المقابل للجبال
If she mistook the view from there for the view from her seat...
...إن خلطت بين المنظر من هناك والمنظر من مقعدها
I haven't been to the dining car.
لم أذهب لعربة الطعام
If that was a lie to cover up the truth about the transaction...
...إن كانت تلك كذبة لإخفاء حقيقة الصفقة
...then the bomb's...
...فالقنبلة
...in her briefcase!
!في حقيبتها
Not good! Only one minute left!
!تبّاً! تبقت دقيقة فقط
Attention, passengers.
انتباه لكافة الركاب
As using cellular phones may disturb other passengers,
استعمال الهواتف الخلوية قد يضايق بقية المسافرين
we ask that you step onto the outside deck before using your phone.
لذا نأمل منكم الذهاب خارج العربة لاستعمال هاتفكم
That's it! The cell phone!
!هذا هو! الهاتف الخلوي
Now what?
أنت! ماذا الآن؟
Hey! Ran says she'll buy us any yummy food we want!
اسمعوا! تقول ران-نيتشان أنها ستشتري !لنا أيّ طعام لذيذ نريد
Alright! I'll take an eel boxed lunch!
!رائع! أريد علبة غداء أنقليس
I want sushi!
!أنا أريد سوشي
I'd like a full course of French cuisine!
!وأنا أريد وجبة طعام فرنسي كاملة
Hey, wait...
...تـ-تمهلوا
It's impossible to plan for someone to press a key or button
...من المحال أن تخطط لضغط أحد لمفتاح أو زرّ
on a laptop or tape player at exactly 3:10!
على حاسب محمول أو مشغل صوت !في الساعة 3:10 تماماً
But a phone!
...لكن بالنسبة لهاتف
It's entirely possible to have a predetermined time or phone number!
!من الممكن ضبطه على زمن معيّن ورقم هاتف معيّن
Too late!
!تبّاً
Hello?
مرحباً؟
10 seconds later, the entire bullet train gets blasted into pieces.
في غضون 10 ثوانٍ، سينفجر قطار الطلقة لأجزاء
What was that?
ما كان ذلك؟
W-Who are you...?
مـ-من أنت؟
Conan Edogawa. A detective!
إيدوغاوا كونان، مُتحرٍّ
D-Detective?!
مـ-متحرٍّ؟
Hey, you! What have you done this time?!
أنت! ماذا فعلت هذه المرة؟
I'm just a grade school student though!
!لكني مجرد طالب في الابتدائية
Afterward, the bullet train was stopped
توقف قطار الطلقة بعدها
and Inspector Megure and his men began their investigation.
وبدأ تحقيق المفتّش ميغوري ورجاله
Being late to the wedding was a problem in itself,
كان التأخر عن الزفاف مشكلة بحدِّ ذاته
but things somehow came to an end without anyone getting hurt.
لكن انتهت الأمور دون إصابة أحد بشكل ما
It turns out she bought inside information about the trading market
تبيّن أنها اشترت معلومات داخلية عن سوق التداول
from the two men for 100 million yen.
من الرجلين مقابل 100 مليون ين
Apparently, she was supposed to call them on a specific phone
ويبدو أنّ كان عليها الاتصال بهما على رقم معين
at a specific time to find out how to open the case.
في وقت محدد لمعرفة كيفية فتح الحقيبة
But the two planned from the start to get rid of her after getting the money.
لكن الاثنين خططا للتخلص منها بعد الحصول على المال من البداية
They were caught and arrested by an emergency police inspection line.
تمّ اعتقالهما من قبل نقطة تفتيش طارئة للشرطة
I really jumped to conclusions though...
...تسرّعتُ بالاستنتاج حقّاً
Where did the real men in black who shrunk me go?!
أين الرجلان بالرداء الأسود اللذان قلّصا جسدي؟
Darn it! I'll never give up!
!تبّاً! لن أستسلم
I'll catch up to you someday!
!سألحق بكما يوماً
I swear it!
!بالتأكيد
Say, Conan-kun. What were you about to tell me that one time?
أخبرني يا كونان-كن، ما الذي كنت تقوله؟
Eh? What are you talking about?
ماذا؟ ما قصدك؟
Don't pretend you don't know! You were serious when you said it!
لا تتظاهر بالحماقة! كانت ملامحك جادة
I'm neither Conan Edogawa nor a grade school student!
...لستُ إيدوغاوا كونان أو طالباً في الابتدائية
I'm...
...أنا
I'm actually...
...أنا في الواقع
Who are you actually?
ما هويّتك بالضبط؟
Uh, I'm actually...
...أ-أنا... في الواقع
A genius at getting into trouble!
!عبقري في الشغب
What are you doing, Ran?
ما الذي تفعلينه يا ران-نيتشان؟
It's chocolate. For Valentine's Day, which only comes once a year!
إنّها شوكولاتة، فالفالنتاين يوم واحد في السنة
A date?!
!موعد؟
I'm going now!
سأخرج إذاً
Go and catch a rich man.
اذهبي واصطادي رجلاً ثريّاً
It goes without saying that this case is an easy one.
إنّها قضية سهلة كما يبدو
Which means you did it!
!أي... أنت الفاعل
The real murderer was...
...الفاعل الحقيقي كان
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Valentine Murder Case.
قضيّة جريمة الفالنتاين
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Chocolate.
شوكولاتة
As always, there is only one truth in the next episode!
!في الحلقة القادمة أيضاً، تبقى الحقيقة واحدة